♪ ♪
Oh, Mom, can you believe this?
Finally, we're here.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I'm really proud of you.
I've been here the night before.
There's a place
downstairs where they say...
Is Joey trying to
kill me or what?
I told him those interviews
were at noon, not 2:00.
But he said that you told him...
Connie, get Joey.
Honey, I'm getting ready
to take care of the wardrobe
first, before we even...
Janet?
Oh, it is. Don.
Oh, oh, oh. Oh, hi.
Hey.
You haven't changed.
And you... why, you
look better than ever.
This is my baby.
Mom.
My daughter Lauren.
Well, welcome to
the show. Thank you.
You know, the last
time I heard about you,
you were in, uh, New York.
Mm-hmm. I have a P.R. firm.
It's small, but it's solid.
Donnie, Connie never
gets anything right.
I tell her noon,
she tells you 2:00...
Connie is not the one
who screwed things up.
This is my associate
Joe DeFalco.
Joe DeFalco. Nice to meet you.
How do you do.
This is Janet and
Lauren Masters.
Janet... she was
our first winner
on Reach For the
Stars. No kidding?
And Lauren is going to be
a real contender this year.
Hey, this is great publicity.
"Daughter Repeats
Mother's Triumph."
Can't buy an angle
like that, right? Yeah.
Oh, Joey.
We'll have a
drink later. All right.
Joey. JOEY: What?
Dana, hi!
Are you ready for this?
Oh, as ready as I'll ever be.
Look, I got to get
signed in, okay?
Okay. Bye. See you later. Okay.
- Janet and Lauren Masters.
- Welcome.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Here we go. Okay.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
And welcome to the 26th
Annual Reach For the Stars
competition.
Tonight our panel of five judges
will decide which of
these talented women
will wake up tomorrow
morning a star.
They will decide who will
win the two-year contract
with Monument Studios,
a brand-new automobile
and $25,000 in cash.
Now, all of this
is made possible
by our Reach For
the Stars sponsor...
New Image Cosmetics.
And before we go any further,
I would like you to meet
the president of New Image...
Mr. Roger Anderson.
Each year, Mr. Anderson chooses
one of our finalists to be
his New Image cover girl.
And so you can bet he will
be watching very closely.
But enough talk.
Let us get on with the show.
♪ Every time I see you ♪
♪ Boy, I can't deny ♪
♪ Some new emotion
shakes me up ♪
♪ Everything I'm feeling ♪
♪ Takes me by surprise ♪
♪ I've kept it to myself
for long enough ♪
♪ Every night I'm dreaming
to wake up to your touch ♪
♪ You're my friend and though
you've been the very best ♪
♪ There's no one better ♪
♪ I will bow to
your one request ♪
♪ Be my lover ♪
♪ 'Cause I want you ♪
♪ I want to feel you melting ♪
♪ All over me, boy ♪
♪ Be my lover ♪
♪ I have to tell you ♪
♪ That I got to have you ♪
♪ Right here right
next to me, boy. ♪
From night clubs
all over the country,
Dana Williams.
From deep in the heart of Texas,
Abby Smith.
♪ There's a place
where lovers go ♪
♪ To cry their troubles away ♪
♪ And they call it
Lonesome Town ♪
♪ Where the
broken hearts stay. ♪
May I present Lauren Masters.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the moment we've
all been waiting for.
In this envelope are the
names of these four women.
Three of them are
about to be runners-up
and one is about
to become a star!
Ladies and gentlemen,
our third runner-up, Abby Smith.
Our second runner-up,
Dana Williams.
Well, ladies and
gentlemen, here we are.
One of these women is about
to become the first runner-up...
The other our winner.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our first runner-up,
Morgan Gerard.
Well, of course,
ladies and gentlemen,
our winner, Lauren Masters!
Morgan?
Over here.
I got your note.
So how does it
feel... tomorrow's star?
What do you want?
Everything.
The contract, the car,
the money, everything.
You're crazy.
You want everyone to know
that your mother was in prison?
You wouldn't.
In a second.
Unless, of course,
you were to...
disqualify yourself.
So that they declare
you the winner?
So they declare me the winner.
You're so smart.
So...
what's it going to be?
The brass ring for me,
or for Mommy,
her poor little face
spread all over the tabloids?
Wouldn't that be awful?
I'll kill you first.
I lost an earring.
You have until midnight.
I'll be in my room.
Lauren?
Just leave me alone, please.
Whoa...
Hello?
Mm.
Huh.
♪ Miss your voice ♪
♪ The touch of your hand ♪
♪ Just long to know ♪
♪ That you understand ♪
♪ My buddy ♪
♪ Your buddy ♪
♪ Misses ♪
♪ You. ♪
You always did love that song.
Oh, Janet.
Janet, Janet, Janet.
Oh... Oh, Janet.
Oh, you look good.
You look good.
Oh, everything I got's
sticking out everywhere.
But you look good!
Ooh! Here, sit down,
sit down, sit down.
Tell me about this
business in the paper.
Ben, my daughter
did not kill that girl,
and I don't know
how to help her.
Where's her father? He's dead.
Oh, that's right.
I'm sorry about that time you...
you spent... In prison.
It was his doing, wasn't it?
I never dreamed that his
real estate deals were crooked.
He'd put a paper in
front of me, I'd sign it.
Well... he was your husband.
Been a long time. Yeah.
I'm gonna tell you something.
I never... I never
said it before,
but, well, I'm gonna tell you.
I was crazy over you.
Well, you never said
anything. Oh, I know, no.
I mean, I was afraid...
You were too pretty.
Everybody was crazy over you.
I wish you'd said something.
I almost did one time.
Remember...
remember that-that time
a bunch of us went
up to Elkton, Virginia?
Mm. The Bluegrass Festival?
Yeah, yeah. I do,
and-and we ended up alone
in your car and you got lost.
Yeah, and we
spent the night in a farmhouse.
And that sweet
farm lady... she gave us some...
milk gravy and biscuits,
Milk gravy, biscuits.
And she sent us off
to bed. Yeah, yeah.
She knew we weren't married.
You slept in a feather bed.
And you slept in the barn,
with a mule named Henry.
Henry.
If I hadn't been
in the barn with that mule,
I feel secure I would've
said something.
Oh, sure. Or if the mule
had been in the feather bed
and I'd been in the
barn with you... Ben?
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh,
Michelle, come on in.
Michelle Thomas, my associate.
Uh, this is Janet Masters.
How do you do? Hello.
Janet's daughter has
been charged with murder,
and we're gonna represent her.
Oh.
Yes, I told Morgan
that I'd kill her.
Well, she threatened
my mother. Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. And this, uh,
this other contestant, uh...
Dana Williams. Yeah.
She heard you?
Yes.
Now Mom's prison
record's all over the news.
Mm-hmm.
Well, after your
fight with Morgan
you went back to the party?
That's right. Told your mother?
That's right. Mm-hmm.
And you didn't
tell anybody else?
You just went straight
up to Morgan's room?
I went up there to tell
her that the title was hers.
And she was dead
when I got there.
I-I just panicked.
Mm-hmm.
The trial will be
set in this courtroom
the 23rd at, uh... 9:00 a.m.
Concerning the
matter of the bail
for the defendant,
uh, Lauren Masters,
does the prosecution
have any recommendation?
Your Honor, the defendant has
no family or professional
ties to this community.
Therefore, flight to
avoid prosecution
is a very real possibility.
We recommend that
bail be set at $100,000.
Oh, Your Honor, uh, my
client has no prior record,
no convictions, no arrests,
not even a traffic ticket.
Her youth alone dictates
that bail should be
no less than $100,000.
She's 20 years old.
That is hardly mature.
Your Honor, she
needs adult supervision.
And she has it.
Her mother's right here.
Her mother is also a
stranger to this community.
Well, not to me... I've known
Janet Masters for years.
I'll vouch for her.
You will? Well,
of course I will.
Mr. Matlock, Ms. March!
Thank you for your attention.
The bail is set at $50,000.
Thank you, Your Honor.
You ready for lunch?
Well, yeah. Uh...
Ben? Meet you outside?
Uh, yeah, mm-hmm.
So, I'll, uh... I'll
see you later?
If I'm still here.
Mm.
This won't take long, Dana.
Come on in here...
and tell me about this.
There's no one here but us.
So, you told the police?
I didn't want to
tell them, but...
they questioned me.
That night after you left
Morgan's dressing room,
did you tell anyone
what you'd overheard?
Yeah, I-I shouldn't have.
But I went back to the party,
and I told Don Mosher, and...
and he was standing with
Joey DeFalco and Mr. Anderson.
And you told them about
the blackmail attempt
and that Morgan had gone
back up to her room alone?
I was just so upset; I-I
blurted everything out.
Second runner-up, huh?
Yeah.
It's my best yet.
But now with the
first runner-up dead
and the winner on
trial for the crime...
you could wind up with that
Hollywood contract, couldn't you?
No. I-I didn't kill Morgan.
But there were rumors about her.
What kind of rumors?
Well, like she'd do
anything to win, including...
well, you know, with the judges.
She slept with the judges?
Mm-hmm.
And she was sleeping
with some VIP at the finals.
Well, at least that's
what the rumors were.
I didn't see anyone,
and neither did anyone else.
So maybe the rumors
were just rumors.
Hi, Carl. I'll just be a minute.
Okay. Wait.
Thanks.
Hmm.
Not exactly a natural
beauty, was she?
Oh, hi, Julie.
I thought you'd get
here a lot sooner.
Must've been a long lunch.
Uh... Julie, uh,
let-let me... let me explain.
Uh, Janet and I are just...
two... old friends.
What were you years ago?
Uh, well, just two...
very young friends.
Oh.
Oh, and you've been
thinking about
her all these years.
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no.
It's just... It's just what?
Well, just, uh...
j... just, you know.
I know what you mean.
Imagine...
well, say, Clay
Ferentol just suddenly...
walked back into my life.
Clay Ferentol?
Mm-hmm. He's the
guy I dated for a while
right after my divorce.
The Clay Ferentol?
That was tight end for
the Dallas Cowboys?
Yes, that's the one.
Anyway, imagine he just
suddenly looked me up
right out of the blue.
You used to date
a pro football player?
Mm-hmm.
So... what if he took
me for long lunches?
How long did you date him?
This isn't going
very well, is it?
Sure it is... I got your point.
Well, uh,
there didn't seem to
be any forced entry.
I noticed that.
Oh, that's, uh, Michelle.
I-I told her... where I'd be.
Hello?
Mm, mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah, uh-huh.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Uh-huh, yeah, okay, okay.
Yeah. Bye.
That was Mich-Michelle.
So, uh...
how often do you hear
from this, uh, Ferentol fella?
Sundays.
I think it'll work out.
Well, I'm just not
feeling good about this...
New Image Cosmetics
has never been in such
a compromising position.
Oh. Oh, hi.
Uh, I'm Ben Matlock,
Lauren Masters' lawyer.
Mr. Anderson? Oh, uh...
Mr. Anderson. I'm-I'm
sorry, Mr. Anderson,
I couldn't stop
him. That's all right.
What can I do for
you, Mr. Matlock? Well,
I understand that
you're thinking
of taking the "Reach
for the Stars" title
away from Lauren.
That's none of your
business, Mr. Matlock.
Well, it-it is.
See, you take that
title away from her,
and it's the same
as saying she's guilty.
The news media would
have her convicted
before she ever goes to court.
That's unfortunate, but
I can't permit scandals
to tarnish the reputation
of New Image Cosmetics.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
But how about
this? How about this?
You stand by Lauren.
You say, "This is America.
A person is innocent
until proven guilty."
New Image would come
out smelling like a rose.
I don't think that's
a very good idea.
America would flock to
New Image. Mr. Matlock...
Your profits would soar!
What do you think?
I like it, I do.
Oh, but you can't...
Get DeFalco on it.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Well, so these are
the, uh... contestants.
Good-looking women there.
These are the finalists.
Each year I pick one of them
to be my, uh, New Image
Cosmetics cover girl.
I'd already decided
who the winner would be,
and the next thing I
knew, she was murdered.
Oh. You had chosen
Morgan Gerard.
Did you tell anybody?
I never got the chance.
You know, there's a rumor
that Morgan was, uh...
How do you say? Seeing somebody
during the contest;
somebody involved
in the contest.
Mr. Matlock, that would
have been against the rules.
You saying Morgan
Gerard wouldn't break rules?
I never break the rules.
Oh, oh. Well,
thanks for your help.
And... oh, does New
Image make a aftershave?
I'd like to kind
of get on board.
Mr. Matlock, I just
want to apologize
for coming on so strong.
Oh, you had a point.
Not valid, but a point.
I wouldn't do anything
to hurt Janet Masters.
She's an old friend.
And God knows she's been
through enough already.
Oh, she has, hasn't she?
I'm a friend, too.
An old friend?
Oh, yeah. I've known her
since before she went to prison.
You know about that?
Oh, I've known her for 26 years.
Of course I knew about that.
I understand you were with
her the night of the party.
What time did she leave?
Oh, 11:15, 11:30.
Oh!
What a nice idea:
dinner at Templin's.
Just like old times.
Yes, you, the music,
even the pretzels.
Yeah, yeah. Nothing's changed.
Well, Ray Junior's on piano.
Go get 'em, Ray!
I got 'em!
Look at these.
Oh, you saved
all these pictures.
Look at all of us.
Those were great times for me.
Was my hair ever that brown?
Sure was.
Damn that mule, right?
How's it going, Ben? Have
you found out anything?
Well, uh, I talked
with Don Mosher.
You know... Well, of
course you know him.
Uh... he said
you left the party about 11:30.
Yes, I did. My daughter
had just told me
she was being blackmailed.
I didn't feel like sticking
around and making small talk.
Where'd you go?
I went for a walk.
I needed some air.
A girl was killed
between 11:30 and 12:00.
I... I sure hope
somebody saw you.
Oh, I don't believe this.
Do you
really think that I
murdered Morgan Gerard
and let Lauren take the blame?
Oh, no. Oh, no, no!
Do you think that I would just
sit here and talk over old times
with you while
Lauren went to prison?
Oh, no, no, Janet, no!
You go to hell.
Hi.
You've, uh, got some company.
Mm? Mm-hmm.
I am just so sorry
about blowing up
at you last night?
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I had no reason...
You had every right to
ask me those questions.
I really had no reason.
Let me just tell you something.
I've been at this so long
that I wake myself
up at night sometimes
saying, "Where were you
at the time of the murder?
"Can you corroborate
that? Was there a witness?
Do you have an alibi?"
Do you ever answer yourself?
Sometimes. Let's
go have some coffee.
I'm telling you I got an angle.
I can double your bookings.
Hey, listen, I gotta go.
No, no, no, you
think about it, okay?
What can I do for
you, sweetheart?
Uh, Michelle Thomas.
Michelle. That's
good. Have a seat.
So what are you into, Michelle?
Singing, acting, modeling, what?
Uh, answers.
Mm-hmm.
I'm an attorney
for Lauren Masters.
Attorney?
What a waste of what you got.
Um, what is all this?
I thought you were
working for Don Mosher.
No, Mosher's a dinosaur.
As soon as I set up
my agency, I'm gone.
Well, I bet you met
a lot of potential clients
setting up Reach
For The Stars for him.
That was the idea.
Were you gonna
sign Morgan Gerard?
Maybe.
Is that why you were
sleeping with her?
Who told you that?
See, you forgot to be
nice to the little people.
Or at least to make sure that
when you pay someone off
not to talk, the
check doesn't bounce.
Whoever the
creep is, he's lying.
Well, that's why
we have courts...
To figure out who's
lying and who isn't.
See you there.
Ben, I want you to know
I've asked to be
reassigned from the case.
Reassigned? Why?
I just think this is
one of those times
when our professional
rivalry might damage
our personal relationship.
Oh, well... It's my call.
Well, who's, uh,
who's replacing you?
Dave Hawkins.
Dave Hawkins?
You're having Hangman
Hawkins replace you?
You think he's
tougher than I am?
Oh, uh... Ben, you called
him "Hangman Hawkins."
Well, yeah. Do you ever
call me names like that?
I call you lots of names behind
your back. I've never heard you.
Well, I've never heard you.
I'm not gonna go right up to
Dave Hawkins and say, "What
say, Hangman? How's tricks?"
Just fine, Ben. See you inside.
Prosecution calls Mrs.
Janet Masters to the stand.
21 years ago, you
were convicted of fraud.
You served eight
months in prison.
Is that correct?
Well, you see, my
husband... Yes or no.
Yes.
Now you own and run
a public relations firm
in New York City.
According to this
profit and loss report,
you made a very nice
profit last year, didn't you?
Yes, we did.
Before the murder
of Morgan Gerard,
and the subsequent publicity,
how many of your clients
knew that you'd been in prison?
None.
How many know now?
I have no idea.
How many clients have you lost
because of the disclosure
of your prison record?
I object. None of this
has anything whatsoever to do with
the innocence or guilt of my client.
It goes to motive, Your Honor.
This witness is the
defendant's mother.
What affects her
affects the defendant.
Overruled.
How many clients have
you lost, Mrs. Masters?
I'm not sure.
Well, four, five?
Six?
Your Honor?
The witness will
answer the question.
Eight. Eight.
You're not gonna be in
the black this year, are you,
Mrs. Masters? No.
And that's why you kept
your prison record a secret,
because you knew your clients
would leave you, didn't you?
Yes or no, Mrs. Masters?
Yes.
And Lauren knew
this, too, didn't she?
But she didn't...!
Yes or no?
Yes!
Which is why she went
up to Morgan Gerard's room
that night and murdered her!
Objection! Objection!
She did no such thing!
I'll withdraw it, Your Honor.
Nothing further, Your Honor.
Oh, Janet feels terrible
about her testimony.
Oh, she did the best she could.
That Hangman
Hawkins is really good.
Yeah. Well, anyway, here's
the credit check on Joey DeFalco.
He owes everybody:
clothing stores,
landlord, phone company.
He used to drive a red
Corvette. Repossessed.
Mm. You suppose he was using
Morgan Gerard to stay afloat?
I'm sure he'd use anybody.
How do you think Morgan knew
about Janet's prison record?
I mean, very few people.
Oh, I don't know, I don't know.
She couldn't have
just stumbled onto it.
Somebody had to have told
her or she found some kind of...
Now, when you first met
Janet Masters and were told
that she was the first
Reach For The Stars
contest winner 26 years ago,
what did you do?
What do you mean, what did I do?
Well, you didn't see this
mother-and-daughter angle
as something you could
exploit in the media?
I recognize that.
Yeah. Well, what
did you do about that?
Nothing. I didn't know
if Lauren would win.
You went ahead and
prepared a press kit, didn't you?
Yes, I prepared a
press kit. Mm-hmm.
And, and you went to where
Don Mosher keeps his files
on his contest winners,
and you, you took Janet's file.
No.
Are you sure?
Because, uh, uh,
her file is missing,
and of all 26 files, hers is
the only one that's missing.
You sure you don't have it?
It'd be very embarrassing
if the police got a warrant
and found that you did.
Now hold on. I, uh,
I remember now.
I think I do have
that file. Yeah.
That's right. I took it
so I could go over it.
Go over it. Yeah, sure,
sure. So what was in it?
Some old photos, Don's notes.
Mm-hmm. Were there
any press clippings?
Don't remember.
If I told you that Don Mosher
specifically remembers
putting clippings
about Janet's conviction
in her file, would that
refresh your memory any?
Okay, so I saw them.
Saw it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, who did you
tell about them?
Nobody.
Not even Morgan Gerard?
Why would I do that?
Well, I understand you
want to be a talent agent.
Yeah. No big secret.
Especially for young
girls... Young, pretty girls.
What can I say? I like girls.
I see.
I also understand
that you're pretty heavy
in debt all over town.
So?
So, you were counting on
Morgan winning that contest,
signing with you as
your first big client
and getting you
out of debt, right?
She was gonna sign with me.
From watching rehearsals,
you knew if anybody was gonna
beat Morgan, it would be Lauren,
so you told Morgan
about Janet's past.
So, if Lauren did win,
Morgan could
blackmail her into losing.
And it worked.
Except Morgan
double-crossed you, didn't she?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
She signed with TLM
Talent Agency in Los Angeles,
didn't she?
And you found out
about it at the party.
I heard about it.
Yeah. I guess it
made you pretty mad.
It made me mad, yes.
Mm-hmm. You know,
Nobody remembers seeing
you at the party after 11:30.
Where did you go?
That's my business.
You went up to Morgan's
room, didn't you?
Nope. And you killed her.
No, I did not.
Where did you go, Mr. DeFalco?
Oh, hell, why not?
I was in... Dana Williams' room.
We were engaged in... uh...
pre-contractual negotiations.
Hey! I'm sorry, baby.
Nothing further.
Ben!
Wait!
Oh, hi, Julie.
I hear it didn't go
very well in there.
Well, Hangman Hawkins
ain't singing the blues.
Come on. Lunch is on me.
Okay.
Hey.
What will it be?
Steak, barbecue, or how
about a nice grilled trout?
Ah...
Everybody and his brother
has been over this room.
Well... Well, we might
as well do it again.
You know what the song says.
Everything's better
the second time around.
This is New Image
Cosmetics' entire line.
Yeah.
Uh, there's three
fingernails missing from this...
line right here.
They're hard to put on?
Well, the hardest part is
putting them on straight.
Huh... Can you get me those
autopsy pictures, will you?
Uh, now, your company,
New Image Cosmetics,
has sponsored
the Reach for the Stars
contest for-for how long?
Seven years. Seven years.
And how long have
you known Joe DeFalco?
He came aboard two years ago.
Do you know him well?
We're not friends.
Well, why would you
give him $45,000?
What makes you think I did that?
He told me you did.
I asked him
how he got back his
repossessed sports car,
and he told me
that he told you that
if you didn't give him $45,000,
he was going to tell the police
about you and Morgan Gerard.
Joey is a special
kind of dude, isn't he?
Took about five
minutes for him to tell me.
Joey's the one who
introduced you to Morgan
when she was competing
in Nashville, isn't he?
Oh, yes, but...
Is-is-is that when your
affair with her started?
No.
Oh, come on.
And it wasn't Joey that
she was seeing on the sly
during the competition
here in Atlanta.
It was you, wasn't it?
No!
And it was because
of your affair
with her that you made her
the new Image Cover girl.
Right?
No, there was no
personal relationship.
Oh, I know there was
no personal relationship.
There was no care.
There was no real love.
I imagine, at times,
your relationship got...
How'd you call...
pretty intense,
till you found out that
she was just using you.
She didn't want you,
just you, she wanted to
be the New Image cover girl.
She wanted a lot of things,
and she would do anything
she had to to get them.
She spent some time with
Joey. Did you know that?
Over the years, there were a lot
of beautiful New
Image cover girls.
But Morgan...
she was the only one, the
only one that you fell in...
How'd you call that?
That wonderful
middle-aged love with.
She's the one that
made a fool out of you.
No! Objection!
Counsel's badgering the witness.
He's trying to pass
off his wild speculation
as questions.
Mr. Matlock, I don't
feel entirely comfortable
about this line of
questioning, either.
Uh, Your Honor, I
have to level with you.
I don't feel
comfortable, myself.
Uh, would you mind
telling us what this is?
That's an artificial fingernail
kit put out by my company.
Uh-huh. And how does it work?
You just, uh...
You peel this little thing off
here and then just stick it on?
Uh, yes, there is glue on the
adhesive backing for each nail.
I see. Now, this was found
In Morgan Gerard's room,
so I guess we can assume
that she was wearing
these false fingernails
when she was killed, and
they came from this kit.
That make sense?
I suppose so.
Now, how many, how many
nails come in these kits?
20, two complete sets.
Twenty.
Now, there are 13 missing.
These and these...
These three right
here. Why would she
replace just three nails?
Well, they could chip or
break off or even fall off
if they're not properly applied.
Well, I thought
all you had to do
was just stick it on, like that.
Well, you have to hold it in
place for at least ten seconds
to allow the, uh, glue
to bond to the nail.
Uh-huh.
Now, let me show you this.
This is a part of the
People's Exhibit 15.
It's an autopsy photograph.
This is the
decedent's right hand.
Now, would you
just take a look at that
and describe these nails to us.
Looks like some of the
fingernails are on crooked. Yeah.
These three right here.
The coroner told me
that when they were
scraping under these nails...
You know, for
bits of skin, hair...
These three nails right
here just fell right off.
And he put them
back the best he could,
but why would these
three just fall right off?
Objection, Your Honor.
Overruled. Oh, I'm
sorry, Your Honor.
Mr. Matlock, I'll be the judge.
Overruled.
Answer the question.
Yes.
I... Well, they were put
on improperly, I suppose.
Or maybe the person
who put them on,
put them on very hastily
and didn't have time
for the glue to hold.
Maybe the killer.
How would I know that?
When Morgan Gerard
double-crossed Joey DeFalco,
then he double-crossed
her by telling you
that she'd been
sleeping around on you.
And I imagine a fellow like you,
that would make you pretty hot.
You went up to her room
that night, didn't you?
No, I didn't. Of
course, you did.
And you confronted her
with what Joey had told you.
You know, about sleeping
on the wrong side of the bed.
And maybe she
said, "Yes, I have."
Or maybe she said,
"What's it to you, old man?"
Or maybe she said, "Go to hell.
How about it?" How
about you going to hell?
And during your lovers' quarrel,
you bludgeoned her,
but she fought back.
She lashed out at you,
and that's how she broke
those nails, clawing at your skin.
Your Honor!
And you saw the nails
on the floor. You
picked them up,
put them in your pocket, quick.
You knew your skin was on them.
And you replaced them
with these three, didn't you?
You can't prove this!
Just pull down your
turtleneck sweater.
What?
Pull down your sweater
a little bit, so we can see
the gouges Morgan made,
clawing at you. I
don't have any gouges.
Pull it down. Just pull it
just a little. Get out of here.
Okay. Okay, but I'll tell you.
When the judge or
three or four cops
want you to pull
down that sweater,
you're going to pull
down that sweater.
Reasonable doubt,
Your Honor, for my client.
That's all I have to
prove, Mr. Anderson.
Reasonable doubt.
We, the jury, find the
defendant not guilty.
Not guilty verdict is
entered into the record.
This court is adjourned.
Well, here we are.
I'm so happy.
Oh, so am I.
I'll never forget
this, Ben, never.
There's a lot of
things I won't forget.
Ben, you did a great job.
Hi, Julie.
You must be very relieved.
We both are.
We're anxious to get home.
You're leaving right away?
Oh, first thing in the morning,
as soon as we're packed.
Oh.
So, tell me, what names do
you call me behind my back?
Honey.
www.tvsubtitles.net